<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<application>
  <id type="desktop">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="ast">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="ca">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="ca-valencia">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="de">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="en-GB">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="es">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="nl">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="pt">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="sk">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="sv">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="uk">org.kde.Falkon.desktop</id>
  <id type="desktop" xml:lang="x-test">xxorg.kde.Falkon.desktopxx</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="ast">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="ca">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="ca-valencia">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="cs">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="de">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="en-GB">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="es">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="fr">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="nl">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="pt">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="sk">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="sv">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="uk">CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <metadata_license xml:lang="x-test">xxCC0-1.0xx</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="ast">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="ca">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="ca-valencia">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="cs">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="de">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="en-GB">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="es">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="fr">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="nl">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="pt">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="sk">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="sv">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="uk">GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <project_license xml:lang="x-test">xxGPL-3.0+xx</project_license>
  <name>Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkonxx</name>
  <summary>Web Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Restolador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Navegador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navegador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Webový prohlížeč</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Webbrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Web Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Navegador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Navigateur Web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Webbrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Navegador Web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Webový prehliadač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Webbläsare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Переглядач інтернету</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxWeb Browserxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">网页浏览器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
    Falkon is a new and very fast QtWebKit browser. It aims to be a lightweight web browser available through all major platforms. This project has been originally started only for educational purposes. But from its start, Falkon has grown into a feature-rich browser.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Falkon és un navegador QtWebKit nou i molt ràpid. Pretén ser un navegador web lleuger, disponible a través de totes les principals plataformes. Aquest projecte només es va iniciar originalment amb finalitats educatives. Però des del seu inici, el Falkon s'ha convertit en un navegador ric en característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Falkon és un navegador QtWebKit nou i molt ràpid. Pretén ser un navegador web lleuger, disponible a través de totes les principals plataformes. Este projecte només es va iniciar originalment amb finalitats educatives. Però des del seu inici, el Falkon s'ha convertit en un navegador ric en característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Falkon is a new and very fast QtWebKit browser. It aims to be a lightweight web browser available through all major platforms. This project has been originally started only for educational purposes. But from its start, Falkon has grown into a feature-rich browser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Falkon es un nuevo y muy rápido navegador basado en QtWebKit. Pretende ser un navegador web ligero disponible para todas las plataformas más populares. Este proyecto se inició originalmente con fines educativos. Aunque, desde el principio, Falkon se ha ido convirtiendo en un navegador rico en funcionalidades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Flacon is een nieuwe en zeer snelle QtWebKit-browser. Zijn doel is om een lichtgewicht webbrowser te zijn beschikbaar via alle belangrijke platformen. Dit project is oorspronkelijk gestart alleen gestart voor onderwijsdoeleinden. Maar vanaf zijn start is Falcon gegroeid in een functierijke browser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Falkon é um navegador novo e muito rápido em QtWebKit. Pretende ser um navegador Web leve e disponível em todas as plataformas importantes. Este projecto foi iniciado originalmente para fins educativos. Porém, desde o início, o Falkon cresceu para um navegador rico em funcionalidades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Falkon är en ny och mycket snabb QtWebKit-baserad webbläsare. Den har som mål att vara en lättviktig webbläsare tillgänglig på alla större plattformar. Projektet startades ursprungligen bara i utbildningssyfte, men från starten har Falkon växt till en funktionsrik webbläsare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Falkon — нова і дуже швидка програма для перегляду інтернету на основі QtWebKit. Метою проекту є створення невибагливого до ресурсів переглядача інтернету для усіх основних програмних платформ. Реалізацію проекту було розпочато з навчальною метою. Втім, з того часу Falkon стала повноцінним переглядачем.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkon is a new and very fast QtWebKit browser. It aims to be a lightweight web browser available through all major platforms. This project has been originally started only for educational purposes. But from its start, Falkon has grown into a feature-rich browser.xx</p>
    <p>
    Falkon has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Falkon té totes les funcions estàndard que s'esperen d'un navegador web. Inclou adreces d'interès, historial (ambdós també a la barra lateral) i pestanyes. A més, podeu gestionar els canals RSS amb un lector RSS inclòs, bloquejar els anuncis amb un complement AdBlock integrat, bloquejar el contingut Flash amb Click2Flash i editar la base de dades de certificats de la AC local amb un gestor SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Falkon té totes les funcions estàndard que s'esperen d'un navegador web. Inclou adreces d'interés, historial (ambdós també a la barra lateral) i pestanyes. A més, podeu gestionar els canals RSS amb un lector RSS inclòs, bloquejar els anuncis amb un complement AdBlock integrat, bloquejar el contingut Flash amb Click2Flash i editar la base de dades de certificats de la AC local amb un gestor SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Falkon has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Falkon posee todas las funciones estándares que cabría esperar de un navegador web. Incluye marcadores, historial (ambos disponibles también en una barra lateral) y pestañas. Además, puede gestionar fuentes RSS con el lector RSS que incluye, bloquear publicidad mediante un complemento integrado, bloquear contenido Flash con Click2Flash y editar la base de datos local de certificados con un gestor SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Falcon heeft alle standaard functies die u verwacht van een webbrowser. Het bevat bladwijzers, geschiedenis (ook in de zijbalk) en tabbladen. Bovendien kunt u RSS-feeds beheren met een ingevoegde RSS-reader, ads blokkeren met een ingebouwde AdBlock plug-in, Flash-inhoud blokkeren met Click2Flash en de lokale database met CA Certificaten met een SSL-beheerder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Falkon tem todas as funções-padrão que iria esperar de um navegador Web. Inclui os favoritos, o histórico (ambos na barra lateral) e páginas separadas. Para além disso, pode gerir fontes RSS com um leitor de RSS incluído, o bloqueio de anúncios com um 'plugin' do AdBlock incorporado, o bloqueio de conteúdos em Flash com o Click2Flash e a edição da base de dados de Certificados da AC locais com um gestor de SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Falkon har alla standardfunktioner man kan förvänta sig av en webbläsare. Det omfattar bokmärken, historik (båda också i sidorad) och flikar. Förutom det, kan man hantera RSS-kanaler med en inbyggd RSS-läsare, blockera reklam med ett inbyggt insticksprogram för reklamblockering, blockera Flash-innehåll med Click2Flash och redigera den lokala certifikatdatabasen för certifikatutfärdare med en SSL-hanterare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У Falkon ви знайдете усі можливості типової програми для перегляду інтернету. Передбачено можливість користування закладками, журналом перегляду (ці дві можливості реалізовано і на бічній панелі) та вкладками. Крім того ви можете отримувати подачі новин RSS за допомогою вбудованого засобу читання RSS, блокувати рекламні повідомлення за допомогою вбудованого додатка блокування реклами, блокувати включення Flash за допомогою додатка Click2Flash та редагувати локальну базу сертифікатів CA за допомогою засобу керування даними SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkon has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.xx</p>
    <p>
    Falkon's main aim is to be a very fast and very stable QtWebKit browser available to everyone. There are already a lot of QtWebKit browsers available, but they are either bound to the KDE environment, not actively developed or very unstable and miss important features. Falkon, a multi-platform, modern and actively developed browser, is here to fill this gap by providing a very stable browsing experience.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'objectiu principal del Falkon és ser un navegador QtWebKit molt ràpid i molt estable per a tothom. Ja hi ha molts navegadors QtWebKit disponibles, però estan lligats a l'entorn del KDE, no estan desenvolupats activament o són molt inestables i no tenen característiques importants. El Falkon, un navegador multiplataforma, modern i desenvolupat activament, és aquí per omplir aquest buit proporcionant una experiència de navegació molt estable.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'objectiu principal del Falkon és ser un navegador QtWebKit molt ràpid i molt estable per a tothom. Ja hi ha molts navegadors QtWebKit disponibles, però estan lligats a l'entorn del KDE, no estan desenvolupats activament o són molt inestables i no tenen característiques importants. El Falkon, un navegador multiplataforma, modern i desenvolupat activament, és ací per omplir este buit proporcionant una experiència de navegació molt estable.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Falkon's main aim is to be a very fast and very stable QtWebKit browser available to everyone. There are already a lot of QtWebKit browsers available, but they are either bound to the KDE environment, not actively developed or very unstable and miss important features. Falkon, a multi-platform, modern and actively developed browser, is here to fill this gap by providing a very stable browsing experience.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El principal objetivo de Falkon es ser un navegador basado en QtWebKit muy rápido y muy estable, y estar disponible para todo el mundo. Ya hay disponibles muchos navegadores basados en QtWebKit, pero están ligados al entorno KDE, no se desarrollan de forma activa o carecen de funcionalidades importantes. Falkon, un navegador web multiplataforma, moderno y activamente desarrollado, está aquí para rellenar este hueco proporcionando una experiencia de navegación muy estable.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Falcon's hoofddoel is een erg snelle en erg stabiele QtWebKit browser te zijn beschikbaar voor iedereen. Er zijn al veel QtWebKit-browsers beschikbaar, maar ze zijn ofwel gebonden aan de KDE omgeving, niet actief in ontwikkeling of erg onstabiel en belangrijke functies ontbreken. Falcon, een multi-platform, moderne en actief ontwikkelde browser, is hier om dit gat te vullen door een erg stabiele ervaring met browsen te bieden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O objectivo principal do Falkon é ser um navegador Web muito rápido e muito estável em QtWebKit, estando disponível para todos. Já existem muitos navegadores baseados em QtWebKit disponíveis, mas ou estão associados ao ambiente de trabalho do KDE, ou não estão em desenvolvimento activo ou ainda estão muito instáveis e com funcionalidades importantes em falta. O Falkon, um navegador multi-plataforma, moderno e em desenvolvimento activo, está aqui para preencher este vazio, oferecendo uma experiência de navegação muito estável.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Falkons viktigaste mål är att vara en mycket snabb och stabil QtWebKit-baserad webbläsare tillgänglig för vem som helst. Det finns redan många QtWebKit-baserad webbläsare tillgängliga, men de är antingen bundna till KDE-miljön, inte aktivt utvecklade eller mycket instabila och saknar viktiga funktioner. Falkon, en modern och aktivt utvecklad webbläsare för flera plattformar, är här för att fylla tomrummet genom att erbjuda an mycket stabil webbläsarupplevelse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Основною метою проекту Falkon є створення дуже швидкої і дуже стабільної, доступної усім програми для перегляду інтернету на основі QtWebKit. Існує вже доволі багато програм для перегляду інтернету на основі QtWebKit, але їх або прив'язано до графічного середовища KDE, або розвиток цих програм припинено, або вони є дуже нестабільними, або у них не реалізовано важливі можливості. Falkon — програма, яка здатна працювати на багатьох платформах, сучасна та така, що активно розвивається, — заповнює потрібну нішу у програмному забезпеченні, надаючи власним користувачам дуже стабільні можливості з перегляду сторінок інтернету.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkon's main aim is to be a very fast and very stable QtWebKit browser available to everyone. There are already a lot of QtWebKit browsers available, but they are either bound to the KDE environment, not actively developed or very unstable and miss important features. Falkon, a multi-platform, modern and actively developed browser, is here to fill this gap by providing a very stable browsing experience.xx</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default" width="864" height="567" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome.pngxx</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="948" height="638" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.pngxx</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="864" height="567" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/screens/dial_gnome.pngxx</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="944" height="633" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.pngxx</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="809" height="528" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/screens/preferences_gnome.pngxx</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="760" height="518" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_preferences.pngxx</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="ast">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="ca">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="ca-valencia">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="cs">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="de">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="en-GB">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="es">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="nl">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="pt">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="sk">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="sv">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="uk">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <url type="homepage" xml:lang="x-test">xxhttps://www.qupzilla.com/xx</url>
  <updatecontact>nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="ast">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="ca">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="ca-valencia">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="cs">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="de">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="en-GB">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="es">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="nl">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="pt">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="sk">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="sv">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="uk">nowrep_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
  <updatecontact xml:lang="x-test">xxnowrep_at_gmail.comxx</updatecontact>
</application>
