<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.falkon.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Falkon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkonxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Falkon</name>
  <summary>Web Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Restolador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Navegador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navegador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Webový prohlížeč</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Webbrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Web Browser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Navegador web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Verkkoselain</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Navigateur Web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Browser web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Webbrowser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka sieciowa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Navegador Web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Webový prehliadač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Webbläsare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Переглядач інтернету</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxWeb Browserxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">网页浏览器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
    Falkon is a new and very fast Qt web browser. It aims to be a lightweight web browser available through all major platforms. This project has been originally started only for educational purposes. But from its start, Falkon has grown into a feature-rich browser.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Falkon és un navegador Qt nou i molt ràpid. Pretén ser un navegador web lleuger, disponible a través de totes les principals plataformes. Aquest projecte només es va iniciar originalment amb finalitats educatives. Però des del seu inici, el Falkon s'ha convertit en un navegador ric en característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Falkon és un navegador Qt nou i molt ràpid. Pretén ser un navegador web lleuger, disponible a través de totes les principals plataformes. Este projecte només es va iniciar originalment amb finalitats educatives. Però des del seu inici, el Falkon s'ha convertit en un navegador ric en característiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Flacon is een nieuwe en zeer snelle Qt-webbrowser. Zijn doel is om een lichtgewicht webbrowser te zijn beschikbaar via alle belangrijke platformen. Dit project is oorspronkelijk gestart alleen gestart voor onderwijsdoeleinden. Maar vanaf zijn start is Falcon gegroeid in een functierijke browser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Falkon jest nową i bardzo szybką przeglądarką sieciową Qt. Jej celem jest być dostępną na wszystkich głównych platformach. Projekt zaczął się ze względów edukacyjnych, lecz od jego początków Falkon stał się bogatą w możliwości przeglądarką.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Falkon é um navegador novo e muito rápido em QtWebKit. Pretende ser um navegador Web leve e disponível em todas as plataformas importantes. Este projecto foi iniciado originalmente para fins educativos. Porém, desde o início, o Falkon cresceu para um navegador rico em funcionalidades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Falkon är en ny och mycket snabb Qt webbläsare. Den har som mål att vara en lättviktig webbläsare tillgänglig på alla större plattformar. Projektet startades ursprungligen bara i utbildningssyfte, men från starten har Falkon växt till en funktionsrik webbläsare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Falkon — нова і дуже швидка програма для перегляду інтернету на основі навігатора Qt. Метою проекту є створення невибагливого до ресурсів переглядача інтернету для усіх основних програмних платформ. Реалізацію проекту було розпочато з навчальною метою. Втім, з того часу Falkon стала повноцінним переглядачем.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkon is a new and very fast Qt web browser. It aims to be a lightweight web browser available through all major platforms. This project has been originally started only for educational purposes. But from its start, Falkon has grown into a feature-rich browser.xx</p>
    <p>
    Falkon has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Falkon té totes les funcions estàndard que s'esperen d'un navegador web. Inclou adreces d'interès, historial (ambdós també a la barra lateral) i pestanyes. A més, podeu gestionar els canals RSS amb un lector RSS inclòs, bloquejar els anuncis amb un complement AdBlock integrat, bloquejar el contingut Flash amb Click2Flash i editar la base de dades de certificats de l'AC local amb un gestor SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Falkon té totes les funcions estàndard que s'esperen d'un navegador web. Inclou adreces d'interés, historial (ambdós també a la barra lateral) i pestanyes. A més, podeu gestionar els canals RSS amb un lector RSS inclòs, bloquejar els anuncis amb un complement AdBlock integrat, bloquejar el contingut Flash amb Click2Flash i editar la base de dades de certificats de l'AC local amb un gestor SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Falkon has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Falkon posee todas las funciones estándares que cabría esperar de un navegador web. Incluye marcadores, historial (ambos disponibles también en una barra lateral) y pestañas. Además, puede gestionar fuentes RSS con el lector RSS que incluye, bloquear publicidad mediante un complemento integrado, bloquear contenido Flash con Click2Flash y editar la base de datos local de certificados con un gestor SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Falkonissa on kaikki selaimelta odottamasi toiminnallisuus: kirjanmerkit, historia (kumpikin myös sivupalkissa) ja välilehdet. Lisäksi voit hallita RSS-syötteitäsi sisään rakennetulla RSS-lukuohjelmalla, estää mainokset sisään rakennetulla AdBlock-liitännäisellä, estää Flash-sisällön Click2Flashillä sekä muokata paikallista CA-varmennetietokantaa SSL-hallintatyökalulla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Falkon dispose de toutes les fonctionnalités standard que l'on peut attendre d'un navigateur. Il comporte des signets, un historique (tous deux également disponibles dans la barre latérale) et des onglets. En plus de cela, vous pouvez gérer des flux RSS grâce au lecteur RSS intégré, bloquer les publicités avec le module externe AdBlock intégré, bloquer les contenus Flash avec Click2Flash et modifier la base de données de certificats CA locaux en utilisant un gestionnaire SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Falkon ha tutte le funzioni standard che ti aspetteresti da un browser web. Include i segnalibri e la cronologia, entrambi anche nella barra laterale, e le schede. Puoi inoltre gestire i feed RSS con un lettore RSS incluso, bloccare sia le inserzioni con un'estensione AdBlock integrata, sia i contenuti Flash con Click2Flash, ed infine modificare la banca dati dei certificati CA con un gestore SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Falcon heeft alle standaard functies die u verwacht van een webbrowser. Het bevat bladwijzers, geschiedenis (ook in de zijbalk) en tabbladen. Bovendien kunt u RSS-feeds beheren met een ingevoegde RSS-reader, ads blokkeren met een ingebouwde AdBlock plug-in, Flash-inhoud blokkeren met Click2Flash en de lokale database met CA Certificaten met een SSL-beheerder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Falkon ma wszystkie standardowe funkcje, których oczekuje się od przglądarek. Zawiera zakładki, historię (zarówno obie na pasku bocznym) i karty. Poza tym, może obsługiwać kanały RSS przy użyciu załączonego czytnika, blokować reklamy przy użyciu wbudowanej wtyczki AdBlock, blokować treści Flash przy użyciu Click2Flash i dedytować lokalne certyfikaty UC przy użyciu zarządzania SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Falkon tem todas as funções-padrão que iria esperar de um navegador Web. Inclui os favoritos, o histórico (ambos na barra lateral) e páginas separadas. Para além disso, pode gerir fontes RSS com um leitor de RSS incluído, o bloqueio de anúncios com um 'plugin' do AdBlock incorporado, o bloqueio de conteúdos em Flash com o Click2Flash e a edição da base de dados de Certificados da AC locais com um gestor de SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Falkon har alla standardfunktioner man kan förvänta sig av en webbläsare. Det omfattar bokmärken, historik (båda också i sidorad) och flikar. Förutom det, kan man hantera RSS-kanaler med en inbyggd RSS-läsare, blockera reklam med ett inbyggt insticksprogram för reklamblockering, blockera Flash-innehåll med Click2Flash och redigera den lokala certifikatdatabasen för certifikatutfärdare med en SSL-hanterare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У Falkon ви знайдете усі можливості типової програми для перегляду інтернету. Передбачено можливість користування закладками, журналом перегляду (ці дві можливості реалізовано і на бічній панелі) та вкладками. Крім того ви можете отримувати подачі новин RSS за допомогою вбудованого засобу читання RSS, блокувати рекламні повідомлення за допомогою вбудованого додатка блокування реклами, блокувати включення Flash за допомогою додатка Click2Flash та редагувати локальну базу сертифікатів CA за допомогою засобу керування даними SSL.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFalkon has all standard functions you expect from a web browser. It includes bookmarks, history (both also in sidebar) and tabs. Above that, you can manage RSS feeds with an included RSS reader, block ads with a built-in AdBlock plugin, block Flash content with Click2Flash and edit the local CA Certificates database with an SSL manager.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Falkon 包含所有浏览器的高级功能，包括书签、历史、侧边栏和标签页。您可以通过内置的 RSS 阅读器管理 RSS 资源，通过内置的 AdBlock 插件屏蔽广告，通过 Click2Flash 屏蔽 Flash 内容，通过 SSL 管理器编辑本地 CA 认证数据库。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.qupzilla.com/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_window.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/kde_speeddial.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome_window.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.qupzilla.com/screens/gnome_speeddial.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
